

Hamza Tarique

Mern Stack Developer

My Contact

hamzatarique2000@gmail.com

(L) +<u>923179654961</u>

Karachi,Sindh

Portfolio

Hard Skill

- MUI
- Tailwind CSS
- Chakra UI
- Git/Github
- Redux/Toolkit
- Context API
- ExpressJS
- NodeJS
- ReactJS
- MongoDB

Soft Skill

- Self-Motivated
- Decision making
- challenging
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- University Of Sindh Bachelors In Information Technology 2019-2022
- Govt Boys High School (KGM)
 Intermediate in Pre Engineering
 Completed in 2018
- Govt Boys High School (KGM)
 Matriculation in Science
 Completed in 2015

About Me

I am an aspirant Mern Stack Developer and passionate about frontend, and backend technologies. I am responsible for writing reusable, testable, and efficient code and developing and designing front end web applications with two years of experience

Work Experience

Mern Stack Developer

Feb 2023 - Present (Ghani Business Solution)

Key responsibilities:

- Responsible for coding APIs in nodejs/expressjs
- Responsible for integrating APIs in frontend usaully in ReactJS
- Responsible for handling state management in ReactJS with (Redux, Redux toolkit and context API).
- As a senior I provide guidance and support to internies throughout the training program

Mern Stack Developer

Oct 2022 - Feb 2023 (Kxsoft)

Key responsibilities:

- Responsible for coding APIs in nodejs/expressjs
- Responsible for integrating APIs in frontend usaully in ReactJS

Mern Stack Developer

Jan 2021- Feb 2023 (Bachelors)

Key responsibilities:

- In this whole period I created many mern projects you may check my <u>Github</u> account and <u>portfolio</u>
- In FYP I created mern project (University Stock System) by own....
 where I added many features like
- invoice genration
- · email sending using nodemailer
- · filteration with many features
- · Stock maintenance and many more

Languages

- English (Conversational)
- Urdu (National)
- Panjabi (Native)